# Jaon Micle

Shenyang, Liaoning, China



jaonmicle@outlook.com



linkedin.com/in/jaon-micle-740105197



+86 18240133892



https://jaonmicle.now.sh

## Summary

I am a software developer with over 7 years of professional experience and an experienced web and mobile developer trained in Node, React, iOS, and Javascript.

I was studying computer science at Beijing Technology and Business University and I've started working on small and middle projects in the third year of study.

In 2012 I've graduated with a Master of Computer Applications degree and started to work in the Fu Xian Song Technology Co, Ltd. I've started as a junior full-stack developer, and during my career there between June 2012 and January 2017 grown up to the senior full-stack developer. After acquiring enough skills I've decided to become a self-employed developer and now work as a freelancer.

I've participated as a senior software engineer in racquet sports reservations and scheduling club events system of Opark, Inc from March 2019 and interacted with the team effectively offering suggestions on both logical and physical design to assure that the system built would be resilient and bulletproof into the future.

As a result, the user utilization rate of the system was increased from 20% to 100%.

I can help you in customizing apps, portals or websites according to your business needs. I make sure to deliver quality projects within a given timeframe as customer satisfaction is always the first priority for us.

# **Experience**



### Senior Software Engineer

Opark Inc

Mar 2019 - Present (1 year 7 months +)

I've participated as a senior software engineer in racquet sports reservations and scheduling club events system of Opark, Inc from March 2019 and interacted with the team effectively offering suggestions on both logical and physical design to assure that the system built would be resilient and bulletproof into the future. As a result, the user utilization rate of the system was increased from 20% to 85%.



#### iOS Developer

#### TM INFORMATION SYSTEMS LTD

Jul 2017 - Oct 2018 (1 year 4 months)

I've participated in the Envoy system development of TM Information Systems LTD as an iOS developer from July 2017 to October 2018 and I've developed the Driver and Passenger iOS app for the Envoy system.

This system is a world-class all-in-one software for a taxi, private hire, chauffeur, airport transfer, executive travel, and limousine companies.

### **Education**



#### Beijing Technology and Business University

Master of Computer Applications - MCA, Computer Software Engineering

I was studying computer science at the Beijing University of Technology which disregarding its main specification provides the best IT education in our region.

In 2012 I've graduated with a Master of Computer Applications degree.

# Skills

Node.js • React.js • MongoDB • AngularJS • iOS Development • Android Development • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • JavaScript • HTML5 • Amazon Web Services (AWS)